{
    "id": "d046eafe30a643ff919351285bd5c9b0",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He eats nothing ………………. burgers.",
            "description": "But can mean except after words like all, none, nothing, any etc.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "except",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you ………………………… the car to the service center tomorrow?",
            "description": "Take is used for movements to places where neither the speaker nor the listener is.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "bring",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Shaheen has agreed to ……………………………. her camera.",
            "description": "We use bring for movement to a place where the speaker or the listener will be.",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "bring",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I always ………………………….. before I go to bed.",
            "description": "Bathe means to take a bath.",
            "answers": [
                "bath",
                "bathe",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt …………………………….. I was fainting.",
            "description": "As if and as though mean the same. We use them to talk about what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay in my apartment …………………………….. we split the rent.",
            "description": "All of these expressions are used to state conditions.",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "so long as",
                "on condition that",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she would bring along ………………………………",
            "description": "The articles cannot be used with possessives. Instead we use a structure with ‘a …. of mine/yours/hers etc.’",
            "answers": [
                "a friend of her",
                "a friend of hers",
                "a her friend"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my phone. Where is ………………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "your's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She lived …………………………….. in a small town.",
            "description": "The correct expression is determiner + whole + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "her whole life",
                "whole her life",
                "her the whole life"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It took two times ………………………… .. I had expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "longer than",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of us ……………………………… problems.",
            "description": "A verb after each of is usually singular however, it can be plural in a more informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. bad health, she quit her job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Due to",
                "Owing to",
                "Because of",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}